<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) 2011 ETH Zurich.
  All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
  are made available under the terms of the GNU Public License v2.0
  which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
  http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html
  
  Contributors:
      Paolo Carta - Implementation
      Theus Hossmann - Implementation
      Dominik Schatzmann - Message specification
-->
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, BluetestActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Twimight</string>
    <string name="app_label">Twimight</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search tweets and users</string>
    <string name="permDescription">This permission will grant access to content providers. Data might be manipulated by malicious applications</string>
    
        <!--  DeviceListActivity -->
    <string name="scanning">scanning for devices...</string>
    <string name="select_device">select a device to be added</string>
    <string name="none_paired">No devices have been paired</string>
    <string name="none_found">No devices found</string>
    <string name="title_paired_devices">Paired Devices</string>
    <string name="title_other_devices">Available Devices</string>
    <string name="button_scan">Scan for devices</string>
    <string name="conditions">By clicking &quot;I Agree&quot; below, I agree to join the Twimight Beta data
collection. The Twimight Beta application will collect data that samples
Twimight application usage statistics and my location during application
usage.

I understand that access to any data collected will only be allowed
to the members of the Twimight research team and only for the purpose of
research performed in the context of the Twimight project. Any published
results of this study will only refer to anonymised and obfuscated data,
and aggregated statistics that do not reveal the identities of the
participants. As a participant I have the right to opt out of this study at
any time during this experiment by uninstalling the application. Moreover,
I have the right to access any information in the data set related to me,
and request for all collected data to be removed. As a user of Twimight
Beta I may participate in the Twimight Beta online competition.</string>
    <string name="dis_mode_description">If you loose Internet connectivity, activate the disaster mode hit
the &quot;D&quot; button in the menu bar. Disaster tweets will epidemically
spread among all phones in disaster mode, without the need for
Internet infrastructure (3G, WLAN).Note that while the disaster
mode is active, your phone will not connect to the Internet through
WLAN. If you need Internet connection and you are in range of a WLAN
access point, disable the disaster mode.</string>
    
</resources>
